<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:arxiv="http://arxiv.org/schemas/atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>arXiv.org - Artificial Intelligence</title>
    <link>http://arxiv.org/list/cs.AI/recent</link>
    <atom:link href="http://arxiv.org/rss/cs.AI" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <description>Computer Science - Artificial Intelligence (cs.AI) updates on arXiv.org</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 05:00:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>arXiv.org</generator>
    <managingEditor>rss-help@arxiv.org</managingEditor>
    <skipDays>
      <day>Saturday</day>
      <day>Sunday</day>
    </skipDays>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advances in Explainable AI: A Novel Approach to Interpretable Deep Learning Models</title>
      <link>http://arxiv.org/abs/2305.00001</link>
      <description>arXiv:2305.00001 Announce Type: new
Abstract: We present a new method for improving the interpretability of deep learning models, focusing on neural networks used in critical decision-making processes. Our approach combines layer-wise relevance propagation with attention mechanisms to provide more accurate and human-understandable explanations of model predictions.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">oai:arXiv.org:2305.00001</guid>
      <category>cs.AI</category>
      <category>cs.BIO</category>
      <arxiv:announce_type>new</arxiv:announce_type>
      <dc:creator>Alice Johnson, Bob Smith</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Learning in Dynamic Environments: Adaptive Policy Optimization</title>
      <link>http://arxiv.org/abs/2305.00002</link>
      <description>This paper introduces a novel reinforcement learning algorithm designed to handle rapidly changing environments. We demonstrate how our adaptive policy optimization technique outperforms traditional methods in scenarios where the environment's dynamics shift unpredictably.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 09:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <category>cs.AI</category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">http://arxiv.org/abs/2305.00002</guid>
      <arxiv:announce_type>replace-cross</arxiv:announce_type>
      <dc:creator>Charlie Brown, Diana Lee</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards General AI: Integrating Symbolic and Sub-symbolic Approaches</title>
      <link>http://arxiv.org/abs/2305.00003</link>
      <description>We propose a hybrid AI architecture that combines the strengths of symbolic AI and deep learning. Our framework demonstrates improved performance on a range of tasks requiring both logical reasoning and pattern recognition, potentially paving the way for more general AI systems.</description>
      <category>cs.AI</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://arxiv.org/abs/2305.00003</guid>
      <arxiv:announce_type>replace-cross</arxiv:announce_type>
      <dc:creator>Eva Green, Frank White</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethical AI: A Framework for Incorporating Moral Considerations in Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>http://arxiv.org/abs/2305.00004</link>
      <category>cs.AI</category>
      <description>This paper presents a comprehensive framework for embedding ethical considerations into AI systems. We discuss the challenges of formalizing ethical principles and propose a multi-layered approach that combines rule-based systems with machine learning to make AI decision-making more aligned with human values.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 13:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://arxiv.org/abs/2305.00004</guid>
      <arxiv:announce_type>replace-cross</arxiv:announce_type>
      <dc:creator>Grace Taylor, Henry Ford</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum-Inspired Algorithms for AI: Enhancing Classical Machine Learning</title>
      <link>http://arxiv.org/abs/2305.00005</link>
      <description>We explore how concepts from quantum computing can be applied to classical machine learning algorithms. Our quantum-inspired approach shows significant improvements in optimization speed and solution quality for a variety of AI tasks, without requiring actual quantum hardware.</description>
      <category>cs.AI</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 15:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://arxiv.org/abs/2305.00005</guid>
      <arxiv:announce_type>replace-cross</arxiv:announce_type>
      <dc:creator>Irene Curie, Jack Turing</dc:creator>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
